Here it is.
ここです
You've arrived.
着いたね
This is amazing.
すごいね、これ
This is orange picking.
これがみかん狩りだね
I have arrived.
着きました
So, do you want to burn a little tangerine?
じゃあ、ちょっとみかん燃えちゃいますか?
Let's burn.
燃えちゃいましょう
I guess I'll just sell it and put it on.
ちょっと売って付けしようか、じゃあ
Isn't it okay here?
ここでいいんでしょ?
Yeah, probably.
うん、多分
Kushan, right here?
クシャン、ここでしょ?
Well, let's go.
じゃあ、行こうか
Mikan is amazing.
みかん、すごい
huge.
でかい
It's quite large.
結構大きい
It's really big.
すごく大きい
That's amazing.
すごいよね
It's so big.
こんなに大きい
Ah, but isn't that a good thing?
あ、でもそこら辺いいんじゃない?
Looks like a good location around here.
ここら辺、場所的に良さそう
Good, good.
いいね、いいね
Cut a second time.
2回目切る
Plastic.
プラね
What do you think?
どうですか?
copper?
どう?
delicious.
美味しい
eat?
食べる?
Eat, eat.
食べる、食べる
This is so sweet.
めっちゃ甘いやん、これ
It's so sweet.
めっちゃ甘いやん
sweet.
甘い
Look over there.
あっちのほう見て
It's not green yet.
まだ緑ないよ
Oh yeah.
あっ ちは
It's true.
本当だ
It's green, right?
緑やん、でしょ?
After all, it's from the sunny side.
やっぱりこっちの日の当たる側面のほうから
Isn't it best to eat around here?
ここら辺で食べるのが一番いいんじゃ?
hey.
ね
delicious.
美味しい
It's cute.
かわいいね
It's sweet and really delicious.
甘くて本当に美味しい
Did you all see it?
みなさん、見た?
Since I came all the way, I put a lot of this in there.
せっかく来てんから、これいっぱい入れたわ
He takes a lot.
いっぱい取ってくれる
You can take all you want with this.
これね、取り放題やからさ
What now?
何今の?
Something was raining.
なんか降ってきた
Maybe it's a leaf?
たぶんそれ葉っぱちゃう?
That's right, I'm adding more and more like that.
そうそう、そんな感じでどんどん入れてるから
It's big.
大きいね
big?
大きい?
huge.
でかい
It's really big.
めっちゃでかいね
Now that's it.
これで、それ
nice.
いいね
That looks really good.
それ、めちゃくちゃ良さそう
It's orange-ish.
オレンジっぽくて
Well then.
じゃーんと
That's nice.
いいですね
It's cute, after all.
かわいいですね、やっぱり
Did the mandarin orange farmer get any?
みかん農家の人、取れましたか?
We have arrived at the mandarin orange farm.
みかん農家に到着だの
Did you get it?
取れましたか?
I got it.
取れました
So let's take a little break, shall we?
じゃあちょっとだけ、休憩しようか、
Above.
上で
It's a bit tiring.
ちょっと しんどいしね
tired.
疲れた
There's something that's been bothering me for a while.
ずっと気になってることがあるんだけどさ
what?
何?
Mandarin oranges are delicious too, though.
みかんも美味しいんだけどさ
Misa-chan, isn't she getting bigger?
みさちゃんってさ、 でかくなってない?
I'm really interested in this.
めっちゃ興味あるんだよね、これ
Can I touch you for a moment?
ちょっと触っていい?
No.
ダメだよ
why?
なんで?
No.
いいや
It's no good outside like this.
こんな外ではダメだよ
There are people.
人いるし
Not there, not there.
いない、いない
No.
ダメだよ
The old man in the tangerine field will cry.
みかん畑のおじいちゃんが泣くでしょ
Don't show me, no.
見せないで、ダメ
Just a little, just a little.
ちょっとだけ、ちょっとだけ
A long time ago, a long time ago.
昔、昔
Oh no, squishy.
やばい、ふにゃふにゃ
Big.
おっきい
By the way, how many cups is this?
ちなみにさ、 何カップあんの、これ?
About H?
Hくらい?
This cup.
この カップ
H cut, what I thought.
Hカット、思いきや
Lots of love, love cup.
愛がいっぱい、愛カップ
I have a lot of dreams, I guess.
夢いっぱいやん、ちょっと
Are you packing your dreams and thoughts?
夢と気を詰めてんの
Really, that's true.
ほんと、そんな、ええから
I'm not worried about anything.
ちょっと、なんも気を触るよ
It's no good.
ダメだって
No, no.
ダメ、ダメ
Erotic.
エロ
This is serious.
これ、マジで
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
There are people there.
人いるしね
picture?
え?
Is there anyone?
人いる?
The love cup is terrible.
愛カップはやばい
Why did you stand up there?
なんでビンビン立ったの?
Why are you standing?
なんで立ってんの?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
What is this?
なんなん、これ
He's already standing.
もう立ってるやん
amazing.
すごい
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
It's kind of perverted.
なんだかんだ、変態なやんな
Misa-chan.
ミサちゃん
kana?
かな?
Misa-chan, you're a pervert.
ミサちゃん、変態なやん
Because it's binging.
だって、ビンビンやで
It feels so good.
めっちゃ気持ちいい
I feel so good
めっちゃ気持ち
good.
いい
Misa-chan, throw it down.
ミ サちゃん、下に投げて
Throw this one down too.
こっちも下に投げて
It feels so good.
めっちゃ気持ちいい
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
I was shocked at first.
最初にショックして
what
なん
in?
で?
Misa-chan, can I lick you?
ミ サちゃん、舐めていい?
why?
なんで?
chatter
喋
It was too much.
り すぎたよ
down.
下す
Is it coming out?
出てるやろ?
With that sickle.
そのカマで
picture?
え?
No, no, no.
だめだめだめ
だめだめ
No.
だめ
Not here.
ここではだめ
I wish it was somewhere other than here.
ここではないところならいいけど
Because I was stabbing you there.
せっかくあそこで刺してたからさ
I wanted to stay like this forever.
このままずっとしたかった
No, it's a little embarrassing to be outside.
いや、さすがに外はちょっと恥ずかしいよ
There were people too.
人もいたし
Do you know?
知ってる?
From that mountain.
その山から
Gikafun, Garin, etc.
ギカフン、ガリンとか
Stay like this forever.
ずーっとこのまま
ずっとこのまま
forever?
ずっと?
I can't stop if I see fruits like that.
あんなフルーツ見せられたら止まらん
Well.
も ん
I wanted to hear my child's voice, but I could hear it.
子供の声も聞きたいのに聞こえたし
Everyone is watching all the time.
みんながずっと見てるよ
big.
大きい
Why are you smiling?
笑顔なんで
I thought it was really big.
めっちゃ大きいなと思って
Don't like big things?
大きいの嫌い?
I like big things.
大きいの好き
You smile so much
めっちゃ笑顔や
yeah.
ん
Misa-chan, it's still hard since you licked it earlier.
み さちゃん、さっき舐めてくれたからずっと硬い
amazing.
すごい
What?
何が?
It's so attractive.
こんだけ魅力的やん
Is it because of Misa-chan?
みさちゃんのせい?
Awesome.
す っごい
Moreover, because she is fair-skinned, she gets really good results.
しかも色白いからめちゃめちゃ結果上げてる
Please wait a moment.
ちょっと 待ってみて
This is amazing.
これすごい
When I was really in trouble.
め っちゃエスラのときに
this?
これ?
eye cup.
アイカップ
huge.
でかい
That's what I'm saying here, Ai.
ここに言ってるもんね、アイって
I'm saying I'm doing it myself
自分でアイやって言ってるもん
hey.
ね
It's embarrassing.
恥 ずかしい
Please go here and try it.
こっちに行ってみてください
It's louder than any other.
どれより音が鳴ってますね
No way.
おらんやん
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
What about your face?
顔は?
Ah, that's embarrassing.
あー恥ずかしい
あー 恥ずかしい
Her hands are also very beautiful.
手もすごい綺麗
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
I like both.
どっちも好き
I'm quitting my position.
私は体勢をやめてる
Elvis' eyes are messed up.
エルビスの目めちゃめちゃやる
Look here.
こっち見て
Below that is amazing.
その下すごい
I want you to show me the bottom.
その下見せてほしい
It's missing from above.
その上から抜けてる
It stands up so much that it's hard to pinch it.
すごい立ってるから、 挟むの大変
I'm trying to get out.
抜け出そうとしちゃう
The system is very spacious and nice.
仕組みもすごい広くていいや
yeah.
ん
Misa-chan, you're all excited here.
ミ サちゃん、ここにギンギンになってる
Since I kept sharpening the chikubi, I don't have to sharpen the chikubi on the contrary.
チクビを削り続けたから、 逆にチクビを削らなくていい
like this?
こう?
Mi
ミ
Sa-chan felt so good that she didn't lick it at all.
サ ちゃん、 気持ち良すぎて全然舐めたり
Let me lick it a little more.
もう少し舐めさせてほら
it hurts.
痛い
feeling
気持ち
good.
良 い
it hurts.
痛 い
Misa-chan, wait a minute.
ミサちゃん、ちょっと
Let's put that in
それ入れちゃお
cormorant.
う
Here.
こ っちね
like this?
こう?